Guide to the Myron Gustin Fincher Papers, 1908-1993
Fincher, Myron Gustin papers, 1908-1993
- Series VIII. Cornell Office Files
  - 1954-1955
    - Chas. Pfizer and Co., 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Purchasing Co., 1954 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Q, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - R, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - S.J. Roberts, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - S, 1953-1955 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - S, 1952-1954 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Sharpe and Dohme Inc., 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - E.R. Squibb and Sons, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Novoxil for N.A. Vet., Squibb, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - R.J. Strasenburgh Co., 1954 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - T, 1953-1955 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Tarbell Farms, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - E.W.Tucker, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - D.H. Udall, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Upjohn Company, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - V, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - W, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - XYZ, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - 1954-1955 (2nd run)
    - A-G, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - H-P, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - R-W, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - 1955-1956
    - A, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - A, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Ambulatory Clinic, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Acriflavine Formula, ca. 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Annual Veterinary Conference, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Antibiotics; Aug.-Ter.-Neo., 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - B, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - C, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - P.D. Camp and Sons, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Clinical Pathological Conference, ca. 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Donald Coye Herd, 1953-1955 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - D, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence -Governor Thomas E. Dewey, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Dilution of Semen, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - E, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - F, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Faculty, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - 1st World Congress on Fertility and Sterility, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Fort Dodge Labs, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Fuerst Stock Farm, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - G, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Graduate School, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Graduate Students, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - H, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Dean Hagan-Appointments, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Dean Hagan-Letters, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Hamilton Pharmacal Company, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Haver-Glover Labs, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - H.G. Hodges, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - I, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - J, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Jensen-Salsbery Labs, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - K, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - L.C. Kent-Letters, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Kings Park State Hospital, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - L, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Library, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Dr. J.V. Lacroix and Dr. Karl Mayer, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Dr. J.V. Lacroix and Dr. Karl Mayer, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Lederle Labs, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - M, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Karl Mayer, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Machold Farms, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Mahrapo Farms, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Mastitis Regional Labs, Canton, Earlville, East Aurora, Farmingdale and Kingston, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Meetings Attended, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Merck & Co., 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - G.E. Morse, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - J.M. Murphy, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - N, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - N.Y.S. Veterinary Medical Society, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - O, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Ortho Pharmaceutical Co., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - P, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Chas. Pfizer and Co., 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Photo Science, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Pitman-Moore, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Purchasing Department, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - R, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - S.J. Roberts, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - S, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - S, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Sharp & Dohme, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - E.R. Squibb & Co., 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - T, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Tarbell Farms, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - U, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - D.H. Udall, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - By Law Revision, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Upjohn Company, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - V, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Veterinary College Operations, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Vibrosis, ca. 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - W, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - C.V. Whitney Farms, 1952-1956 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - XYZ, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 1956-1957
    - A, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - A, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - B, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - B, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - C, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - D, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Dilution of Semen, ca. 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Dwarfism, ca. 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - New Drugs, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - E, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Emerald Bar-S Farms-Cow Herd Exam, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - F, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Faculty Committees, etc., 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - 1st World Congress on Fertility and Sterility, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - G, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Graduate School, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Genetic Problems that should be considered in Selection of Artificial Breeding Bulls, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - H, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - H, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - H, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - H, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - I, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - J, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - K, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - K, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - L, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - M, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - M, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - M, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Mastitis, Central Office, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - New Mastitis Data, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Mastitis Committee - State Society, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Varidase Research, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Coxsacki Institute, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Plans for the Mastitis Program, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Mastitis - Proposed State Programs, II, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Meetings Attended, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - N, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - New York State Veterinary Medical Society, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - O, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - P, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - P, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - P, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - R, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - S, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - S, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - T, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - U, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - University Policy Committee, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Livestock Sanitary Association - Committee on Infectious Disease of Cattle, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - V, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Veterinarians Wanted, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - W, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - X-Y-Z, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Annual Report - Mastitis, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Annual Report, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Annual Report, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Annual Report, 1953-1954 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - 1957-1958
    - A, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Ambulatory Clinic, 1955-1957 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - American Breeders Service (Bartlett and Higley), 1958 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - American Cyanamid, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - American Society for the Study of Sterility, 1956-1958 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - A.V.M.A. Executive Board, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - A.V.M.A. Executive Board, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - A.V.M.A. Group Insurance Office, 1955-1957 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Mastitis Research and Control Program Annual Report, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - N.Y.S. Mastitis Program Annual Report, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Annual Veterinary Conference, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Armour Labs, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Building Project, 1952-1954 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Building Project, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - New Building Project, 1954-1955 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Dr. John Collins, re: FDA Limitations of Penicillin, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Dr. John Collins, re: FDA Limitations of Penicillin, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Dr. John Collins, re: FDA Limitations of Penicillin, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Dr. John Collins, re: FDA Limitations of Penicillin, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - B, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - B, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Badger Breeders Farm, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Class #4 List, 1956-1958 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry-Briefs, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry-Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - C, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Donald Coye's Herd, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - P.D. Camp and Sons, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Clinical Pathology Conference, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - D, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Dewey, Thomas E. (Dapplemere Farm), 1957 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - E, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - F, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Farm and Home Week, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Film Requests, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Fox, F.H., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - G, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - H, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Hagan, W.A.-Letters, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Hamilton Pharmacal Co., 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Hodges, H.G., 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - I, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - J, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - K, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Kent, L.C.-Finances (Budget, etc.), 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Kent, L.C.-Letters, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - L, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Lacroix, J.V., 1957 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Lederele Labs, 1955-1958 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Flower Veterinary Library, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - M, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Machold Farms, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - S.E. Massengill Co., 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Mastitis-Central Office, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Canton, NY, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Earlville, NY, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Mastitis Control Program-East Aurora, NY, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Farmingdale, NY, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Kingston, NY, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - McDonald Farms, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Meetings Attended, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Merck, Sharp and Dohme, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Morse, G.E., 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Murphy, S.M., 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - N, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - New York Artificial Breeders' Cooperative Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - N.Y.S., 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Norden Labs, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - O, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Ortho Research Foundation, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - P, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Chas. Pfizer Co., 1956-1958 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Pitman-Moore, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - R, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Roberts, S.J., 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - S, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - S, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Squibb and Sons, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Students, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Sterility, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - T, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Tarbell Farms, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Tice, A.K., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - U, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - University Faculty Committee, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Upjohn Co., 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - United States Livestock Sanitary Association, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Sterility and Mastitis Teaching Herd, 1955-1957 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - V, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Veterinarians Wanted, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - W, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - C.V. Whitney Farm, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - XYZ, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Medical Department Annual Reports, Mastitis Division, 1954-1958 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Annual Report, July 1, 1956-June 30, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - W.A.H. Annual Report, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Annual Report Medical Department to W.A.H., 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Use to Formulate Dean's Report, 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - 1958-1959
    - Ambulatory Clinic, 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - A, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Abbott Laboratories, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Admissions, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - American Breeder's Service, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association-Executive Board, 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association-Speaker's Kit, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association-Chicago, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Armour Labs, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Professor Brownell's Report on the Livestock of Greece, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - 2-way radio information, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Group III Equipment, ca. 1956 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - B, 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Building Project, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Building Project, 1953-1957 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Building Project-Personnel, New Veterinary College, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry-M.J. Cerosaletti-Director, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry-D.B. Dalyrmple, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - C, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Collins-Limitations of Penicillin, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Departmental Circular Letters, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - D, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Gov. Thomas E. Dewey, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - E, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Electro-Ejaculators, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - F, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Farm and Home Week, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Fertility and Sterility-3rd World Congress, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - G, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Graduate School, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Lectures in Greece, Fulbright, Nov., 1958-Jan. 1959 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - H, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Dean Hagan Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Hamilton Pharmacal Co. Inc., ca. 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Dr. H.G. Hodges, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - I, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - J, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Jensen-Salsbery Labs, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - K, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Grant S. Kaley, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - L.C. Kent Finances, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - L.C. Kent Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - L, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Large Animal Clinic-Seminars, etc., 1959 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Veterinary Library, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - M, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Machold Dairy, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Mastitis Central Office, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Canton, NY, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Earlville, NY, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Mastitis Control Program-East Aurora, NY, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Farmingdale, NY, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Kingston, NY, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Dr. G.E. Morse, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Dr. J.M. Murphy, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - O, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - P, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - P.D. Camp and Sons, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Chas. Pfizer & Co., 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - R, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Dr. S.J. Roberts, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - S, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Small Animal Clinic-Seminars, etc., ca. 1959 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Smith, Kline and French, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - E.R. Squibb and Sons, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - T, 1954-1959 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - C. Nils Tavares-Brooks Law Office, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Tarbell Farms, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - A.K. Tice, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - U, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - U.S. Livestock Sanitary Association, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - V, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Veterinarians Wanted, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - W, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - XYZ, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - 1959-1960
    - A, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Ambulatory Clinic-Instructions, Letters, etc. (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - American Breeder's Service, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - American Cyanamid Co., 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 68)
    - American Society for the Study of Sterility, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - The Cornell Veterinarian-Annual Report, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 70)
    - Ambulatory Clinic-Annual Report, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 71)
    - Annual Report, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 72)
    - Annual Veterinary Conference, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 73)
    - A.V.M.A., 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 74)
    - American Dairy Association and the A.V.M.A.- Comments, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 75)
    - A.V.M.A.-Executive Board #5, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 76)
    - A.V.M.A.-Executive Board #4, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - A.V.M.A.-Executive Board #3, 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - A.V.M.A.-Executive Board #2, 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - A.V.M.A.-Executive Board #1, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Armour Laboratories, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - B, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Beacon Milling Co., 1959 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - British State Medicine (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - C, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - P.D. Camp and Sons, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Circular Letters-Departmental, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Clinical Pathology Conference (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Cornell Veterinarian Inc., 1958 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - D, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Division of Animal Industry (D.A.I.), 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - D.A.I.-M.J. Ceroslaetti, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - D.A.I.-G.S. Kaley, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - T.E. Dewey (Dapplemere Farms), 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - E, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - 40th Reunion, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - F, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Film Requests, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Faculty-Meetings, Committees, etc., 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Farm and Home Week, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - G, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Graduate School, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - H, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Harver Silos, 1956-1959 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Haver-Lockhart Labs, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - H.G. Hodges, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - I, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - J, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - K, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - L.C. Kent-Letters, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - L, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - L.A.C.-Meetings, etc., 1959 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Veterinary Library, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - M, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - M, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - McDonald Farms, 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Machold Farms, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Mahrapo Farms, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Mastitis Central Office, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Amsterdam, NY, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Canton, NY, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Earlville, NY, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Mastitis Control Program-East Aurora, NY, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Farmingdale, NY, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Meetings attended, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Merck Sharp & Dohme, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - G.E. Morse, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - N, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - New York Artificial Breeders' Cooperative, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - New York State Veterinary Medical Society, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - O, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - C.R. Omar-Agricultural Research Service, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - P, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Pitman-Moore Co., 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Poppensiek, G.C., 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Q, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - R, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Reprints Sent, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - S.J. Roberts, 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - S, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Materials on Sterility, 1958-1961 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Pan-American Conference of the International Fertility Association, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Kline and French, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - E.R. Squibb and Sons, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Student Information, 1959-1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - T, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Tarbell Farms, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - U, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Upjohn Co., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - V, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Veterinarians-Interne, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Veterinarians Wanted, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - W, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous loose materials, ca. 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - 1960-1961
    - A, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Antibiotics in Food, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Antibiotic Experiments, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Antibiotics, ca. 1960 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Antibiotics, ca. 1960 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Ankony Farms, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Admissions, 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - American Breeders Service-D.E. Bartlett, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - American Cynamid, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Experimental Staphylococcus Aureous Mastitis Toxiod, 1959-1961 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Coye Herd, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - General Cochrane, 1959-1961 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Warren Farms, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Warren Farms, 1959-1961 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Vet. College Herd, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Annual Report, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Annual Report, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 32)